Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - J
        - Jammers - And you know that, 1982; SR-18090; Jammers (Box 307)
          Catalog # SG 377 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG-377-A
          Salsoul Records
        - Justified Ancients of Mu Mu - Down town, 1987; SR-18091; Justified Ancients of Mu Mu (Box 307)
          Catalog # JAMS 27T; A-side Matrix # JAMS 27 TA-1U-1-1
          KLF Communications
        - Justified Ancients of Mu Mu - Whitney joins the J.A.Ms, 1987; SR-18092; Justified Ancients of Mu Mu; J.A.Ms (Box 307)
          Catalog # JAMS 24T; A-side Matrix # JAMS 24T A2
        - Jana - More than life, 2000; SR-18093; Jana (Box 307)
          Catalog # PR 300248; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-89860-1
          Curb Records
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - Janacek, Leos - Taras bulba; Sinfonietta, 1962; SR-18094; Janacek, Leos; Czech Philharmonic Orchestra; Ancerl, Karel (Box 307)
          Catalog # PLPS-166; A-side Matrix # PLPS 166 A
          Parliament
        - Janice - Bye-bye, 1986; SR-18095; Janice (Box 307)
          Catalog # PRO-424; A-side Matrix # PRO-424-A
          4th & Broadway
        - Janice - Wanna be with you, 1987; SR-18096; Janice (Box 307)
          Catalog # PRO 441; A-side Matrix # PRO 441-A
        - Janine - Moving on, SR-18097; Janine (Box 307)
          Catalog # MIC-601; A-side Matrix # MIC-601-A
          Micmac Records, Inc.
        - Jankel, Chas - Ai no corrida, 1980; SR-18098; Jankel, Chas (Box 307)
          Catalog # SP-17142; A-side Matrix # AMSP 017142-A
        - Jans, Tara - A few good men, 1985; SR-18099; Jans, Tara (Box 307)
          Catalog # FMS 62261; A-side Matrix # FMS-62261-A-RE
        - Janura, Trina - Heat of the night, SR-18100; Janura, Trina (Box 307)
          Catalog # PH 4001; A-side Matrix # PH-4001-A
          Power House Records
          Roslyn Heights, New York
        - Japanese Telecom - Japanese Telecom remixes, 2000; SR-18101; Japanese Telecom (Box 307)
          Catalog # ITU 004; A-side Matrix # ITU 004-A (NSC) ME LOVE YOU LONG TIME
          Intuit-Solar
        - Jared - Fly so high, 1993; SR-18102; Jared (Box 307)
          Catalog # SG-300; A-side Matrix # SG-300 A
          Screamin' Gold Records
        - Jarre, Jean-Michel - Oxygene in the ghetto, 1998; SR-18103; Jarre, Jean-Michel (Box 307)
          Catalog # FDM 3768-6; A-side Matrix # FDM3768 A1
          Disques Dreyfus
          France
        - Jarreau, Al - L is for lover, 1986; SR-18104; Jarreau, Al (Box 307)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2530; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2530-SH1
        - Jarreau, Al - L is for lover, 1986; SR-18105; Jarreau, Al (Box 307)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2568; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2568-SH1
        - Jarreau, Al - L is for lover, 1986; SR-18106; Jarreau, Al (Box 307)
          Catalog # 1-25477; A-side Matrix # 1-25477-A-SR2
        - Jarrett, Keith - Byablue, 1977; SR-18107; Jarrett, Keith (Box 308)
          Catalog # AS-9331; A-side Matrix # AS-9331 A
          Impulse!
        - Jarrett, Mikey - Don't spare me (And spoil the oil), SR-18108; Jarrett, Mikey; Brisset, Bunny (Box 308)
          Catalog # AR-01; A-side Matrix # AR-01-A
          Artistic Reggae Muffin
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Jarrett, Mikey - Don't spare me (And spoil the oil), SR-18109; Jarrett, Mikey; Brisset, Bunny (Box 308)
        - Jasmine - Ain't no stoppin' us now, SR-18110; Jasmine (Box 308)
          Catalog # TSOB 1202; A-side Matrix # TSOB 9002 A
          TSOB Production
          Italy
        - Jasmine - Ain't no stoppin' us now, SR-18111; Jasmine (Box 308)
        - Jasmine - Close to you, 1990; SR-18112; Jasmine (Box 308)
          Catalog # TSOB 1201; A-side Matrix # TSOB 1201 A
        - Jason, Kenny "Jammin" - Jam tracks, 1985; SR-18113; Jason, Kenny "Jammin" (Box 308)
          Catalog # DJ 891; A-side Matrix # DJ-891A
        - Jasper, Chris - Time bomb, 1989; SR-18114; Jasper, Chris (Box 308)
          Catalog # 4Z9 73127; A-side Matrix # XSS-73127 A-1A
          Gold City
        - Jasper St. Co. - God helps those (Who help themselves), 1999; SR-18115; Jasper St. Co.; DJ Spen (Box 308)
          Catalog # BBR-022; A-side Matrix # BBR-022-A
          Basement Boys Records
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - Javier - Crazy, 2003; SR-18116; Javier (Box 308)
          Catalog # SPRO 7087 6 17849 16; A-side Matrix # SPRO-17849-A
        - Jawara, Jali Musa - Soubindoor, 1988; SR-18117; Jawara, Jali Musa (Box 308)
          Catalog # MLPS 9832; A-side Matrix # MLPS 9832 A
          World Circuit
        - Jay-el - Be about yours, SR-18118; Jay-el (Box 308)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # BE ABOUT YOURS A
          Orpheus Music
          Stone Mountain, Georgia
        - Jay Sun N.Y.C. - Ain't havin' it; I'll trip, SR-18119; Jay Sun N.Y.C. (Box 308)
          Catalog # DANCIN HILLS-002; A-side Matrix # DANCIN HILLS-002 -A
          Dancin' Hill Records
          Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania
        - Jay U Experience - Asalama lei kun, 1990; SR-18120; Jay U Experience (Box 308)
          Catalog # DREPS 001; A-side Matrix # DRS-EP-001-A
          Drum Records
          Central Islip, New York
        - Jay-Z - Izzo (H.O.V.A); You don't know, 2001; SR-18121; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # 314 588 701-1; A-side Matrix # 314 588 701-1-A
          Roc-A-Fella Records
        - Jay-Z - Dirt off your shoulder; Encore, 2003; SR-18122; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # DEFR-15998-1; A-side Matrix # B0001936-11-A
        - Jay-Z - Reasonable doubt (Disc one), 2004; SR-18123; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18124; SR-18125; SR-18126. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 50592; A-side Matrix # 04992 50592-1 A
        - Jay-Z - Reasonable doubt (Disc two), 2004; SR-18124; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18123; SR-18125; SR-18126. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 50592; A-side Matrix # 04992 50592-1 C
        - Jay-Z - Reasonable doubt (Disc one), 1996; SR-18125; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18123; SR-18124; SR-18126. Double album.
          Catalog # SPRO 30094; A-side Matrix # 30094 A RE-1
        - Jay-Z - Reasonable doubt (Disc two), 1996; SR-18126; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18123; SR-18124; SR-18125. Double album.
          Catalog # SPRO 30094; A-side Matrix # 50642 C
        - Jay-Z - Do it again (Put ya hands up), 1999; SR-18127; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # 314 562 575-1; A-side Matrix # DEF-406-A
        - Jay-Z - Change the game; You, me, him and her, 2000; SR-18128; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # 314 572 761-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-15227-1-A
        - Jay-Z - Can't knock the hustle, 1996; SR-18129; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # SPRO 30086; A-side Matrix # PVL-53242 A
        - Jay-Z - Can't knock the hustle (Fool's paradise remix), 1996; SR-18130; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18131. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PVL 53251; A-side Matrix # 04992-53251 1 19 PVL
        - Jay-Z - Can't knock the hustle (Fool's paradise remix), 1996; SR-18131; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18130. 2 copies.
        - Jay-Z - The blueprint (Disc one), 2001; SR-18132; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18133. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 15420-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-15240-1-A
        - Jay-Z - The blueprint (Disc two), 2001; SR-18133; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18132. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 15420-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-15241-1-A
        - Jay-Z - 99 problems, 2004; SR-18134; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # DEFR 16058-1; A-side Matrix # B00002484-11-A1
        - Jay-Z - Dirt off your shoulder; Encore, 2003; SR-18135; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # DEFR 15998-1; A-side Matrix # B00001936-11-A
        - Jay-Z - Change clothes, 2003; SR-18136; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18137. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DEFR 15919-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-15919-1-A
        - Jay-Z - Change clothes, 2003; SR-18137; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18136. 2 copies.
        - Jay-Z - Girls, girls, girls; Takeover, 2001; SR-18138; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18139. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 314 588 793-1; A-side Matrix # 314 588 793-1 A
        - Jay-Z - Girls, girls, girls; Takeover, 2001; SR-18139; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18138. 2 copies.
        - Jay-Z - Hovi baby; U don't know (remix), 2002; SR-18140; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # DEFR 15733-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-15733-1A
        - Jay-Z - Izzo (H.O.V.A); You don't know, 2001; SR-18141; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # 314 588 701-1; A-side Matrix # 314-588-701-1-A
        - Jay-Z - The blueprint (disc one), 2001; SR-18142; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18143. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 15420-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-15420-1-A
        - Jay-Z - The blueprint (disc two), 2001; SR-18143; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18142. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 15420-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-15421-1-A
        - Jay-Z - 03 Bonnie & Clyde, 2002; SR-18144; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # DEFR 15715-1; A-side Matrix # 440-063-843-1-A
        - Jay-Z - Can't knock the hustle (fool's paradise remix), 1996; SR-18145; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # PVL 53251; A-side Matrix # 04992-53251-19PVL A
        - Jay-Z - Stop; Excuse me miss again, 2003; SR-18146; Jay-Z (Box 308)
          Catalog # B0000398-11; A-side Matrix # B0000398-11-A1
        - Jay-Z - Dirt off your shoulder; Encore, 2003; SR-18147; Jay-Z (Box 308)
        - Jigga - Brooklyn Finest, SR-18148; Jigga (Box 308)
          Catalog # APX-3550; A-side Matrix # APX-3550-A
        - Jaybok The City Ace - My Masurati; Hip hop phenomal, 1987; SR-18149; Jaybok The City Ace (Box 308)
          Catalog # PAL-7184; A-side Matrix # PAL-7184-A
          Zakia Records
        - Jaybok The City Ace - My Masurati; Hip hop phenomal, 1987; SR-18150; Jaybok The City Ace (Box 308)
        - Jaye, Miles - Heaven, 1989; SR-18151; Jaye, Miles (Box 308)
          Catalog # 0-96508; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-57970-57971-DMM1
          Island Records
        - Jaye, Miles - Objective, 1989; SR-18152; Jaye, Miles (Box 308)
          Catalog # DMD 1306; A-side Matrix # STDM56835-5
        - Jaywalk - Ooh yeah check it out y'all, 1996; SR-18153; Jaywalk (Box 308)
          Catalog # PG7406; A-side Matrix # PG-7406-A
          Pure Genius
          Long Island, New York
        - Jaywalk - Ooh yeah check it out y'all, 1996; SR-18154; Jaywalk (Box 308)
        - Jaz - To your soul, 1990; SR-18155; Jaz (Box 308)
          Catalog # E1-93320; A-side Matrix # E1-93320-Z1
          EMI
        - Jaz - The originators, 1990; SR-18156; Jaz (Box 308)
          Catalog # V-56166; A-side Matrix # V-1-56166-Z2
        - Jaz B. Lat'n - Set it off, 1994; SR-18157; Jaz B. Lat'n (Box 308)
          Catalog # 856 003-1; A-side Matrix # 856-003-1-A
          Mercury
        - Jazé - It's alright, 1998; SR-18158; Jazé (Box 308)
          Catalog # U8P-1346; A-side Matrix # U8P-1346 A
          Universal Records
        - Jazzie Ladies - Blowin' your mind, 1983; SR-18159; Jazzie Ladies (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18160. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRL D668; A-side Matrix # PRLD-668-AS
          Prelude Records
        - Jazzie Ladies - Blowin' your mind, 1983; SR-18160; Jazzie Ladies (Box 308)
          In same jacket as # SR-18159. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRL D594; A-side Matrix # PRLD-594-AS
        - Jazzy Dee - Get on up, 1983; SR-18161; Jazzy Dee (Box 309)
          Catalog # DM 503; A-side Matrix # DM503A-1
          Laurie Records
        - Jazzy Dee - Put it to the test, 1983; SR-18162; Jazzy Dee (Box 309)
          Catalog # 12C-1003; A-side Matrix # 12C-1003A-1
          3C Records
          Norwood, New Jersey
        - Jazzy Jay - Back to the lab, 1988; SR-18163; Jazzy Jay (Box 309)
          Catalog # L33-18088; A-side Matrix # MCA 9554
          UNI Records
        - Jazzy Jay - Son of a beat street; Into the night, 1984; SR-18164; Jazzy Jay (Box 309)
          Catalog # DMD 784; A-side Matrix # ST DM 46763-2
        - DJ Jazzy Jeff - King heroin (don't mess with heroin), 1985; SR-18165; DJ Jazzy Jeff (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18166. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JDI-9330; A-side Matrix # JDI-9330-SA
        - DJ Jazzy Jeff - King heroin (don't mess with heroin), 1985; SR-18166; DJ Jazzy Jeff (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18165. 2 copies.
        - DJ Jazzy Jeff - Mix so I can go crazy, 1985; SR-18167; DJ Jazzy Jeff (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18168. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JD1-9378; A-side Matrix # JD1-9378-SA-1
        - DJ Jazzy Jeff - Mix so I can go crazy, 1985; SR-18168; DJ Jazzy Jeff (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18167. 2 copies.
        - DJ Jazzy Jeff - The magnificent Jazzy Jeff, 1987; SR-18169; DJ Jazzy Jeff; Fresh Prince; DJ Jazzy Jeff and The Fresh Prince (Box 309)
          Catalog # 1030-1-JD; A-side Matrix # 1030-1-JD-A-1
        - DJ Jazzy Jeff - A touch of jazz, 1987; SR-18170; DJ Jazzy Jeff; Fresh Prince; DJ Jazzy Jeff and The Fresh Prince (Box 309)
          Catalog # 1040-1-JDAB; A-side Matrix # 1040-1-JPA
        - DJ Jazzy Jeff - A touch of jazz, 1987; SR-18171; DJ Jazzy Jeff; Fresh Prince; DJ Jazzy Jeff and The Fresh Prince (Box 309)
        - DJ Jazzy Jeff - The magnificent Jazzy Jeff, 1987; SR-18172; DJ Jazzy Jeff; Fresh Prince; DJ Jazzy Jeff and The Fresh Prince (Box 309)
        - DJ Jazzy Jeff - Girls ain't nothing but trouble, 1986; SR-18173; DJ Jazzy Jeff; Fresh Prince; DJ Jazzy Jeff and The Fresh Prince (Box 309)
          Catalog # WD 001; A-side Matrix # WD-001-A
          Word Records
          Philadephia, Pennsylvania
        - Jazzy The Band - Body rock, 1983; SR-18174; Jazzy The Band (Box 309)
          Catalog # JAY 001-A; A-side Matrix # JAY-001-A
          Jazzy Records
          Washington, DC
        - jb³ ‎ - Close grind (disc one), 1996; SR-18175; jb³ ‎ (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18176. Double album.
          Catalog # NoMu50LP; A-side Matrix # NOMU 50 LP A1
          NovaMute
        - jb³ ‎ - Close grind (disc two), 1996; SR-18176; jb³ ‎ (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18175. Double album.
          Catalog # NoMu50LP; A-side Matrix # NOMU 50 LP C1
        - JB's - Food for thought, 1972; SR-18177; JB's (Box 309)
          Catalog # PE 5601; A-side Matrix # THE JB'S 5-34066-RE-1 A
          People
        - J.Boogie's Dubtronic Science - Try me, 2003; SR-18178; J.Boogie's Dubtronic Science (Box 309)
          Catalog # om-130sv; A-side Matrix # om-130-sv-1
          OM Records
          San Francisco, California
        - J.Boogie's Dubtronic Science - Rainfall; Try me; Movin' to my beat, 2003; SR-18179; J.Boogie's Dubtronic Science (Box 309)
          Catalog # OM-147SV; A-side Matrix # OHM-147SV-A
        - JD - Money ain't a thang, 1998; SR-18180; JD; Jay-Z (Box 309)
          Catalog # CAS 41019; A-side Matrix # XSS 41019-A-1A
        - JD - The party continues, 1995; SR-18181; JD; Da Brat (Box 309)
          Catalog # 44 78786; A-side Matrix # XSS78786B-1A
        - JD - Sweetheart, 1995; SR-18182; JD; Mariah (Box 309)
          Catalog # CAS 41331; A-side Matrix # XSS-41331-A
        - JD - The party continues, 1995; SR-18183; JD; Da Brat (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18184. Different discs.
          Catalog # CAS 3573; A-side Matrix # XSS-3573-1A
        - JD - Money ain't a thang, 1995; SR-18184; JD; Jay-Z (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18183. Different discs.
          Catalog # 44 78864; A-side Matrix # XSS 41019 B-1A
        - JD73 - Happy people, 2005; SR-18185; JD73 (Box 309)
          Catalog # WAX-0205; A-side Matrix # 63549F1/A
          Wax On
        - Jean, Evelyn - Chateau noir, 1995; SR-18186; Jean, Evelyn (Box 309)
          Catalog # DIG 031-1; A-side Matrix # DIG 031 A
          Dig It International
        - Jean, Wyclef - We are trying to stay alive, 1997; SR-18187; Jean, Wyclef; Refugee Allstars (Box 309)
          Catalog # 44 78602; A-side Matrix # XSS-78602A
        - Jean, Wyclef - Cheated (to all the girls), 1998; SR-18188; Jean, Wyclef (Box 309)
          Catalog # 44 78993; A-side Matrix # XSS-78993A
        - J.D.L. - The fat boys ate up the food, 1986; SR-18189; J.D.L.; Coldcrush Brothers (Box 309)
          Catalog # K0002-A; A-side Matrix # K-0002-A
          PKO Records
        - Jedd, Bajja - Bed work sensation, 1992; SR-18190; Jedd, Bajja (Box 309)
          Catalog # SIG133; A-side Matrix # SIG-133-A
          Signet Records
        - Jedi Knights - The big ones, 1997; SR-18191; Jedi Knights (Box 309)
          Catalog # EV0043; A-side Matrix # EV0 043-AA1
          Evolution
        - Jeep Beat Collective - Repossesed wildstyles EP, 1998; SR-18192; Jeep Beat Collective (Box 309)
          Catalog # RUF016; A-side Matrix # RUF016 A-1
          The Ruf Label
        - Jeep Beat Collective - Retimed detonation, 1996; SR-18193; Jeep Beat Collective (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18194. Different discs.
          Catalog # RUF013; A-side Matrix # RUF-013-A
        - Various - Ruf diamonds vol 1, 1996; SR-18194 (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18193. Different discs. Various artists.
          Catalog # RUF012; A-side Matrix # RUF-012 A
        - Jeep Beat Collective - Retimed detonation, 1996; SR-18195; Jeep Beat Collective (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18196. Different discs.
        - Jeep Beat Collective - Retimed detonation, 1996; SR-18196; Jeep Beat Collective (Box 309)
          In same jacket as # SR-18195. Different discs.
        - Jeep Beat Collective - Attack of the wildstyle beatfreaks, 1995; SR-18197; Jeep Beat Collective (Box 309)
          Catalog # RUF008; A-side Matrix # RUF008-A
        - Jeep Style - If there's a cure, 1989; SR-18198; Jeep Style (Box 309)
          Catalog # KV 729; A-side Matrix # KV 729 A
          Top Secret Records
        - JefferSeif - Into the groove, 1985; SR-18199; JefferSeif (Box 309)
          Catalog # JS 001; A-side Matrix # JS 001 A
          Jeffer Sief
        - Jefferson, Marshall - The house music anthem, 1986; SR-18200; Jefferson, Marshall (Box 309)
          Catalog # TX117; A-side Matrix # TX-117
          Trax Records
        - Jefferson, Marshall - The house music anthem, 1986; SR-18201; Jefferson, Marshall (Box 309)
        - Jefferson, Morris - To spank with love; Spank your thang, 1978; SR-18202; Jefferson, Morris (Box 309)
          Catalog # RRD 20511; A-side Matrix # RRD-20511-AS
          Parachute
        - Jefferson, Ron - Vous ete's swing, 1976; SR-18203; Jefferson, Ron (Box 309)
          Catalog # CAT-7601; A-side Matrix # SLX-01814
          Catalyst Records
          Rahway, New Jersey
        - Jeffries, Michael - Razzle dazzle, 1986; SR-18204; Jeffries, Michael (Box 309)
          Catalog # 0-20450; A-side Matrix # 0-20450-A-SH2
        - Jelly & Fish - In too deep, 1998; SR-18205; Jelly & Fish (Box 309)
          Catalog # 7243 846095; A-side Matrix # B814100-01 A1 MK
          Virgin Records
        - Jellybean - Sidewalk talk, 1984; SR-18206; Jellybean (Box 309)
          Catalog # SPRO-9288; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9288-Z1
        - Jemini The Gifted One - Funk soul sensation, 1995; SR-18207; Jemini The Gifted One (Box 309)
          Catalog # PRO 1190-1; A-side Matrix # PRO 1190-1A
        - Jena Si Qua - Verse 1, verse 2, 1997; SR-18208; Jena Si Qua (Box 309)
          Catalog # CAS 3106; A-side Matrix # XSS-3106 A
        - Jender, Jesse - Rude boy remember, 1992; SR-18209; Jender, Jesse (Box 309)
          Catalog # CI-70; A-side Matrix # CI-70-A
          Cross Iland Records
        - Jenkins, Kechia - I need somebody, 1987; SR-18210; Jenkins, Kechia (Box 309)
          Catalog # PRO-7180; A-side Matrix # PRO-7180-A
          Profile Records
        - Jenkins, Tomi - Tomi, 1989; SR-18211; Jenkins, Tomi (Box 309)
          Catalog # 60814-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-60814-A-1
          Elektra
        - Jennie - Bring back the bus stop, 1990; SR-18212; Jennie; Nightrains (Box 309)
          Catalog # 2 ON ONE; A-side Matrix # 2ONONE-A
          Elevation Inc
        - Jerky Boys - The Jerky Boys 2, 1994; SR-18213; Jerky Boys (Box 309)
          Catalog # 1-92411; A-side Matrix # 1-92411-A-SR1
        - Jerome - Too old for me, 1998; SR-18214; Jerome (Box 309)
          Catalog # BBDP-9196; A-side Matrix # BBDP-9196-SA
          Bad Boy Entertainment
        - Jerry Harrison: Casual Gods - Rev it up, 1988; SR-18215; Jerry Harrison: Casual Gods (Box 310)
          Catalog # 0-20897; A-side Matrix # 0-20897-A-SH1
          Sire
        - Jeru The Damaja - Ya playin' yaself, 1996; SR-18216; Jeru The Damaja (Box 310)
          Catalog # PR12326-1; A-side Matrix # PR12-326-1A
          Payday
        - Jesse's Gang - Noiz without words, 1986; SR-18217; Jesse's Gang (Box 310)
          Catalog # 0-20527; A-side Matrix # 0-20527-A-SH1
          Geffen Records
        - Jesse's Gang - Back up, 1987; SR-18218; Jesse's Gang (Box 310)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2764; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2764-SH1
        - Jessica - Get up on your feet (Keep on dancin'), 2000; SR-18219; Jessica (Box 310)
          Catalog # RPRO207-1; A-side Matrix # RPRO 207-1 A
          Restless Records
        - Jet - Empty handed, 1981; SR-18220; Jet (Box 310)
          Catalog # TC 2210; A-side Matrix # TC-2210-A-RE-1
          Thirdcoast Records
          Evanston, Illinois
        - Jet Black, O Peso Do Funck - Gemo a noye inteira; Rap do brasileiro, 1995; SR-18221; Jet Black, O Peso Do Funck (Box 310)
          No entry in Discogs
          Catalog # 443.056; A-side Matrix # 443.056
          Amostra Invenda Vel
          Rio De Janeiro, Brazil
        - Jets - Crush on you, 1985; SR-18222; Jets (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18223. 2 copies.
          Catalog # L33-17089; A-side Matrix # MCA-5162-FDS-1
        - Jets - Crush on you, 1985; SR-18223; Jets (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18222. 2 copies.
          Catalog # L33-17089; A-side Matrix # MCA-5140-FDS-1
        - Jets - Rocket 2 U, 1987; SR-18224; Jets (Box 310)
          Catalog # L33-17471; A-side Matrix # MCA-7474-BG4
        - Jets - Private number, 1986; SR-18225; Jets (Box 310)
          Catalog # MCA-23637; A-side Matrix # MCA-5607-FDS-1
        - Jets - Crush on you, 1985; SR-18226; Jets (Box 310)
        - Joan Jett and the Blackhearts - Everyday people, 1983; SR-18227; Joan Jett and the Blackhearts (Box 310)
          Catalog # L33-1121; A-side Matrix # MCA-3594-MD-1
        - Jett, Joan - I love rock & roll; Love is alive, 2003; SR-18228; Jett, Joan; Wright, Gary (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18229. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AO-9528; A-side Matrix # AO9528 A
          Alpha Omega Recordings
        - Jett, Joan - I love rock & roll; Love is alive, 2003; SR-18229; Jett, Joan; Wright, Gary (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18228. 2 copies.
        - Jewel - Stand (disc one), 2003; SR-18230; Jewel (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18231. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 301323; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301323 A-J
        - Jewel - Stand (disc two), 2003; SR-18231; Jewel (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18230. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 301323; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301323 C-J
        - Jewel - Stand (disc one), 2003; SR-18232; Jewel (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18233. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 301324; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301324 A-J
        - Jewel - Stand (disc two), 2003; SR-18233; Jewel (Box 310)
          In same jacket as # SR-18232. Double album.